Alex Quan

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexcquan/

Portfolio: https://alexcquan.github.io/

Summary

Solution-savvy UX/UI Designer with an emphasis on psychology and working knowledge of graphic design combines user research and creativity to design for mobile and web applications. Thrives on creating delightful human-computer interactions, brand loyalty, and customer retention. Experience with high attention-to-details and conflict resolution, and recent graduate of a UX/UI Bootcamp at UCI 2019.

Garden Grove, CA 92840

Email: alexcquan@gmail.com

Phone: (714)804-6080

Technical Skills

- **Psychology**: Organization, Time-Management, Attention-to-Details, Critical Thinking, Data Analyzing, Communication, Abstract Reasoning, Interpersonal, Reporting
- User Experience: User Research, User Testing, Prototyping, Wireframing
- **Graphic Design**: Adobe Creative Suite, Invision App, Prototypes, Mockups
- Front-End Development: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript/JQuery, Bootstrap, WebFlow

Projects

SoundCloud (*Redesign*) | December 2019

Refocusing the SoundCloud brand to portray a diversity of artists and clarify the purpose - "Hear the world's sounds."

Tools: Google Drive, Trello, Google Forms, Miroboard, Adobe XD, StoryboardThat, Invision App https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1XTU5m1rQzy9fKek5nmtSFft5cym1GGK5SaLfIYm27zo/edit?usp=sharing

Games Done Quick (Redesign) | October 2019

Redesign of the Games Done Quick's website to improve the credibility and trustworthiness of the charity game-streaming event.

Tools: Google Drive, Trello, Google Forms, Miroboard, Adobe XD, StoryboardThat, Invision App https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1k3wnUBnaXUChRCrBknUwMnYUFAeXqU5FCTOWOB-5nC g/edit?usp=sharing

Department of Homeland Security (Redesign) | August 2019

Redesign of the Department of Homeland Security website to improve navigation through card sorting and sitemaps as well as implement design-systems along the way to reach the goal.

Tools: Google Drive, Trello, Google Forms, Miroboard, Adobe XD, Invision App, Uxpressia https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1M0-C79ablmoBGU2HKXRJiADvZVIsCb7l6rWy-M9zjAk/edit?usp=sharing

Gamer's Hub (Design) | July 2019

Designs a mobile app to assist gamers to connect with their friends and coordinate game time in a hassle-free manner.

Tools: Google Drive, Trello, Google Forms, Miroboard, Adobe XD, StoryboardThat, Invision App https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1wzPn84UZp1_VBZ07Eci8YS2YRqMeUHGbQn6OzOGIGgk/ed it?usp=sharing

Work Experience

AVID Intern Feb 2019 to May 2019

Sunny Hills High School – Fullerton, CA

Assists academic success amongst high school students in all subjects and wrote a thesis on the AVID program improvements for the next school year.

Casino Banker Feb 2018 to May 2018

ACME Player Services, LLC – Hawaiian Gardens, CA

Uses strong attention-to-detail skills to maintain an accurate count of the bank while ensuring integrity at the game tables. Successfully caught two acts of cheating was acknowledged through the company.

Tutor Nov 2017 to May 2018

Warwar Academy Tutoring - Orange, CA

Helps and teaches the students to learn in all their academic subjects and give progress reports to parents.

Quality Auditor 02/2016 to 06/2016

Oakley Headquarters – Foothill Ranch, CA

Monitors and inspects all details of glassware 100% to Oakley standards and keeps track of defects in production to report to the supervisor at the end of the shift.

Scanner 06/2015 to 10/2015

Skyline Document Solutions – Irvine, CA

Manages multiple projects in an organized manner and ensures the quality of the finished products.

Document Specialist 06/2014 to 02/2015

AppleOne – Irvine, CA

Handles all documents and print needs accurately and quickly to meet company deadlines.

Education

UX/UI Bootcamp Certificate: University of California, Irvine, CA **B.A. Psychology: California State University, Fullerton,** Fullerton, CA